Finding Aid for the Paul Hardacre Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Schilling, William Albert Hayden (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Hollis, Daniel Webster, III (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Hendrix, Nancy Leah (Box 12, Folder 10)
- McCampbell, Alice Elizabeth (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Auffenberg, Thomas Lynn (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Schilling, William Albert Hayden, ed. Gell’s Diary (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Shouse, Sarah Jean Newman (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Fox, George Thomas (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Bussey, Robert Bridgham (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Dixon, Thomas (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Strock, Nancy Parmalee (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Parrish, Martha Lorraine (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Ackerman, Kay E. (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hawthorne, Harry David, Jr. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Hitchin Purwell Field Map (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Habitat in Africa (Box 13, Folder 2)
- America, Partitions of (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Britain, Roman (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Architectural Heritage, Britain’s (Box 13, Folder 5)
- British Isles, Maps of (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Colonization and Trade in the New World (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Counties of England (Box 13, Folder 8)
- England, Geography of (Box 13, Folder 9)
- John Speed’s Map of England, 1611 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- England, E. Waugh’s (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Europe, Maps of (Box 13, Folder 12)
- History 244—Outline Maps (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Local Government Act (1972): Map (Box 13, Folder 14)
- London: Bacon’s Gem Map (of London & Suburbs) (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Normandy, the Battle of (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Ordinance Survey Maps, The Historian’s Guide (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Ordinance Survey, Maps and Services (Box 13, Folder 19)
- South America (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Spanish Southwest, 1528-1793 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- United States of America (Box 13, Folder 22)
- The World (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Hardacre dissertation -1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Hardacre dissertation-2 (Box 13, Folder 25)